# DYLAN KEI

#### FULL STACK DEVELOPER

- +1 (660) 675-4948
- fancydev0225@gmail.com
- Toronto, On, Canada
- https://dylan-kei.netlify.com

### PROFILE

I am an open-minded developer who's ready for new challenges. I spent most of my career in web development. I am confident in my backend experience. Now I am mastering the front-end field and focusing on smart contract development. I love working with great people, inspiring others, and being inspired.

## INTERESTS

- Thirsty of new technology
- · Reading Books
- Motor biking

## SKILLS

- Solidity
- Rust
- Anchor
- Web3.js
- Ether.js
- TypeScript
- React.js
- Angular.js
- Vue.js
- Svelte
- Node.js
- Golang

### EXPERIENCE

#### SENIOR WEB3 DEVELOPER

BitX Finance

01.2022 - 05.2022

- Built DeFi platform which is live on Elrond mainnet.
- Developed whole smart contract written in Rust for Decentralized
  Finance, passed Audit from Spywolf, and Certik
- Lauched apps such as IDO, stake, swap, lock/vesting, LP Farming, NFT mint, NFT staking.
- Contributed to the partnership with other platforms on the chain
- Built North Myth based blockchain game including coin flip, lottery

#### LEAD DEVELOPER

Self Employed

01.2021-12.2021

- Created a multilayered solidity smart contract for retrieving data from block chains and processing it for financial, statistical analysis
- Optimized application in solidity for thread contention
- Optimized incoming channel distribution with a specific algorithm and maintained data integrity across the application

- Python
- Laravel
- Adobe XD
- Figma
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB
- Strong Communication

## EDUCATION

## BACHELOR OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

The University of Tokyo 2012 - 2016

## CERTIFICATE OF ACHIEVEMENT BLOCKCHAIN TECHNOLOGY

University of California, Berkley 2018





- Wrote the main multi threaded module in C++, which conducted the main financial processes
- Contributed to Babyswap platform. Was in charge of smart contract development of yield farming, token developing and swap written in solidity
- Supported cross-functional teams to review specs and provide insights
- Manage subgraphs and work with backend/frontend teams to integrate smart contracts into the entire infrastructure

#### **BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER**

Consensus Base

06.2018 - 12.2020

- Created a permissioned blockchain with the newly implemented consensus
- Developed smart contracts for testing new features
- Contributed to the development of the first and biggest NFT marketplace of Japan called Polkafantasy
- Contributed to one of the biggest mining pools on the AION network
- Participated in development of AMM on DEX site
- Focused on Rust development and developed smart contracts of game platform written in Rust

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER -> PROJECT MANAGER**

CMC Global

11.2016 - 05.2018

- Worked with senior management and technical teams to minimize infrastructure costs while maintaining high availability
- Worked on several business applications and other kinds of software productions from individual client
- Used Microsoft technologies for large-scale business application for example: C#, Angular.js/jQuery, MS SQL Server, Azure
- Implementation of web scrapping with node.js puppeteer and web streaming service with web socket
- Worked on Elasticsearch for advanced search functions and search engine data management through Logstash plugin
- Built back-end with microservices architecture in several stacks development including Laravel, Node.js and Python
- Database administration with PostgreSQL and MongoDB